NYLCE JOY GREJARTE



+639278353662



iamnhelz0624@gmail.com



Country Homes, Bacolod City



PROFILE

Highly motivated Web Developer with experience in building and maintaining web applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and EJS. I am a dedicated, organized, and methodical individual. I have good interpersonal skills and an excellent team worker. I am a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadline.

EDUCATION

Binalbagan Catholic College

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2010 - 2014

KodeGo

Full Stack Web Development March 2023 - August 2023

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, EJS, PHP, MongoDb
- Photoshop
- Microsoft Office (MS Word, MS Excel, PowerPoint)
- Experience in working with people on different levels.

PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

FoodTreep May 2023 - July 2023

- Tools used: Html, CSS, Bootstraps, JavaScript.
- Building Frontend and API of a FoodTreep Website.

Live Link - https://cjbravo28.github.io/FoodTreep/

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Rumeraz Diagnostic Laboratory July 2023 - August 2023

- Tools used: Bootstrap, JavaScript, EJS, mongoDB
- Building the Frontend and Backend of a Rumeraz Diagnostic Laboratory Website.

Live Link -

https://rumerazlab.onrender.com/home?fbclid=IwAR3etp94sJC3lD-

 $_RvfkkLhAACJP0GCxYabHRUGcp9rvzz5NCLqKLVaLWOM$

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer
ACCENTURE | August 08, 2022 - December 13, 2022

- Build Frontend and Backend using Java, JavaScript, React and MySQL.
- •Designs, codes, or configures, test and debugs.
- Responsible for troubleshooting and issue analysis.

Money Sorter BPI | 2021 - 2022

- Sorting cash, including the piece-counting of bills, as well as counting and bagging of coins based on the standards of the BSP.
- Detecting counterfeit bills and insertions.
- Sorting Bills and coins according to the following classifications.
- •Bundling and strapping of bills per denomination.

Money Sorter

Bank of Commerce | 2018 - 2019

- Responsible in sorting bills.
- Verify and secured if every sets of money are hundred pieces.
- Dispensing and funding of cash in ATM.
- Bagging of coins in accordance to BSP standards.
- Compile and file the documents.

Money Sorter

BDO | 2016 - 2017

- Classified money if it's original or not.
- Sorts money manually.
- Verify and secured if every sets of money are hundred pieces.
- Bondless count, verified and handles money.
- Answer calls.

REFERENCES

Marybel Catubig Cash Hub Head Bank of Commerce Lacson, Bacolod City (034) 432-0735

Howard Angel Belonio Asst. Manager Banco De Oro Capitol Shopping, Bacolod City (034) 435-0501/0502